Hey, today we're talking about corsets.
I have different corsets from Corset Story here.
Over-the-brust, full-breast, a under-the-brust corset and a thymid.
And I will create four different looks and show them to you.
Have fun, let's go!
Okay, this is the look.
Very typical for me actually.
Just a leggings to combine with the corset.
We have a over-the-brust corset with a deep neckline made of paint.
On the side there are mesh inserts.
And matching to that is a leggings that is actually made of artificial leather.
Also small paint inserts everywhere.
I think it fits wonderfully together, this material combination.
And because of the paint inserts in the pants, the corset is presented as best as possible.
I also put on a small neckband.
I always like to do that when there is little going on here.
Because of the corset there is a lot of empty space here, but the collar helps optically.
If I would go out and party and then stop, I would tie it a little less extremely.
Just to be a little more comfortable during the evening.
If the top is still a bit too naked, you can of course put on a jacket or a shrapnel.
Or what I like to do to make it a little more poppy is to put on gloves.
This time, of course, also a suit-fit in paint.
Of course, this is not an outfit to go to work with, but rather something I would wear to a party.
In any case, you are at an event, so the looker.
Now it goes on with the next corset.
Now I have a tie-in sweater on, also called the best corset. I come from Westby.
I like to combine such tie-in sweaters with skirts, because they make the transition from the bottom of the skirt to the body beautiful.
I also like to wear something fluffy like these tulle sleeves together with the tulle skirt.
Small hack here, I stuffed the skirt under the tie-in sweater, at least pulled it up at the front and glued it down.
and the lace holds it great.
I like to do that to create the Fukuhila effect on the skirt.
Then you can see the boots or the panties and I don't find it as boring as if the skirt would stop for a long time.
To be honest, of course, it is a bit more comfortable than all other long corsets.
It doesn't press on the hips, you can move better.
I love to wear such outfits for example for a festival all day long.
So of course it's an advantage if the whole thing is just a little more movable.
Next combination, this time quite classic, from a catsuit and a lower-brow corset.
I have to say, lower-brow corsets are my favorite corsets, because they are the most versatile.
You can wear it in virtually all variations.
You can only wear it as underwear, on leggings and a bodysuit maybe underneath.
You can sew wide clothes together and go forward with it.
You can of course also wear tight clothes.
Actually, everything works.
Many corsets from Corset Story have different lengths.
I think that's great. I'm a bit taller, with 173 cm, a bit longer.
So I wear a longline version here.
As the name suggests, it's a bit longer than a regular version.
And it doesn't look too short on me.
Of course, with my blue hair I chose a blue corset.
pink line in the middle gives that again so nice color plex to make up what I
wear that I have for all four courses now left the same I think
a smokey eye always works I have here black and silver combined also because
on the corsets everywhere silver is always when I have a cat in my
videos the questions come in the comments
how do you go to the toilet very simple step-by-step closure is the magic word
absolutely no problem with that anymore I love it yes different cat suits
just to combine with a corset so you can just optically
evaluate so much again and the whole thing a little more layered
make it a very simple option the outfit a little bit to find
next corset next outfit and I think that's the most elegant outfit today
with a full-breasted corset the design here is a bit artsy a bit
I think it fits my hair color very well.
I combined it with a black mini skirt.
I pulled the skirt over the corset.
I also like to do that with some other fabric pants.
It gives the whole thing a sophisticated touch.
I think it's a very nice combination.
Not only to pull the corset over something,
but you can also pull skirts and pants over the corset.
Pay attention to your size of the corset.
corset types just a little bit on your size I have a 75c that fits
perfectly with the over-the-body corset here for a full-breast corset I would recommend
not to have breasts too big that was the last outfit I have to say I think it's better
than expected I was a bit unsure at the beginning with the skirt but it just looks mega good
write me in the comments what was your favorite which outfit did you like best
press the thumbs up button and subscribe to my channel. Also, big thanks to Corset Story
for the corsets and I'll just see you again in the next video. Until then, bye!